CHALERMKHWAN NASRITHA

2519 N Francisco Ave, Unit G, Chicago, IL, 60647 | 224-245-5354 | Chalermkhwan.b.n@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a self-taught web developer who likes to create a new website and make it work perfectly as requirement. I like to learn and solve problems and challenges to improve my skills. I am willing to learn new technology and enhance skills to earn new experience by myself and with people who are interested in technology as well.

EDUCATION

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang, Bangkok, Thailand Bachelor of Computer Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Ready Made Staffing/ Language Resources, Chicago, IL, Thai Interpreter

September 2019 - present

- · Interpret from English to Thai and vice versa accurately, clearly and quickly in court
- Do reports on daily tasks

Oysy Izakaya, Chicago, IL, Hostess & Server

August 2017 – June 2019

- Management of seating and service sections
- Provision of excellent service to ensure customers enjoy their meals
- Bar tending & mixology

Thai Lagoon, Chicago, IL, Server

November 2016 - April 2019

- Provision of full and attentive service for customers
- Management of orders to ensure on-time delivery
- Management of delivery, accounting and end of day close out procedures
- Ability to multitask and stay focused even in hectic situations

EDUCATION & EXPERIENCE

- Volunteering packing food at Greater Chicago Food Depository
- Member of Network Laboratory in college

WEBSITES/ PROJECTS

- www. Keenokthai.com
- www. github.com/khwaniiz
- Collaboration Software for Computer Engineering Department Project

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, MySQL and PHP

Framework & Libraries: React and Bootstrap

Server Technologies: WAMP Tool: GitHub and Visual Studio